This app works best with JavaScript enabled.

Privacy Policy
==============

We, the [Manyverse Developers](https://gitlab.com/staltz/manyverse/blob/master/AUTHORS) are **committed to not collecting any user content nor personally identifiable information** generated by users via the Manyverse app.

By default, the app does not deploy any user data collection mechanism such as analytics, telemetry, cookies, trackers, and others. We simply do not have access to user data, **unless given to us willingly by the users**, such as via bug reports or crash reports.

We work with **third parties** to access information you share with us. These providers are bound by their Privacy Policies to safeguard that information. When using Third-Party Services like GitLab, Sentry, etc. in connection with your sharing of information to us, their Terms and Privacy Policies govern your use of those services.

Bug reports
-----------

If you, the user, choose to send bug reports via the "Email bug report" button in the app, you will do so by sending us an email. The bug report is stored privately on GitLab and only the app developers have access to it, subject to [GitLab's Privacy Policy](https://about.gitlab.com/privacy/).

Since emails always include the sender's address, this means that naturally we would know your email address, and we might answer back regarding your feedback or bug report. We will not share your email address with anyone else, or contact you for any other purpose. Any information you send will be used solely for the purpose of improving the app.

Crash reports
-------------

By default, crashes in the app do not cause any metadata to be sent to any server. However, if you want to help Manyverse developers identify and fix crashes that are happening in the app on your device, you can choose to "Allow crash reports" in the Settings in the app. This means that whenever the app crashes, it will automatically send crash metadata (such as the error's stacktrace, device model, operating system name and version, version of Manyverse) to [Sentry.io](https://sentry.io/). This is subject to [Sentry's Privacy Policy](https://sentry.io/privacy/). These automatic crash reports do not include personally identifiable information (such as location, IP address, SSB identifier, and others). Once users choose to allow automatic crash reports, they can also choose to disallow them.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email the lead developer Andre Medeiros by email at contact@staltz.com

* Resources
    =========

Contact
=======

* Contribute
    ==========

* Team
    ====

The Manyverse app is [open source](https://gitlab.com/staltz/manyverse) software licensed as [Mozilla Public License 2.0](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/MPL/) and copyright by [The Manyverse Authors](https://gitlab.com/staltz/manyverse/blob/master/AUTHORS). The [manyver.se website](https://gitlab.com/staltz/manyverse-site) is licensed as [Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/), copyright by [Andre Staltz](https://staltz.com/).
